# Noman Ali

**Software Developer** 

### **Contact Information**





+92 308 2479593

• Karachi, Pakistan

#### Skills

- Laravel
- Codeigniter
- Php
- VueJs
- Angular
- · HTML/ CSS / Bootstrap
- Javascript
- NodeJs / ExpressJs
- · Python Core
- Mongodb
- · Rest Api's
- MYSQL / PostgreSQL
- · Payment Api's

#### **Certificates**

# Introduction to Programming NodeJs/ Express / Mongodb

**Great Learning** 

#### **Angular**

Coursera

#### Student of the Month

Gexton

#### **Web Development**

Gexton

## **Introduction to Cyber Security**

Coursera

#### **Projects**

- Donation Project
  - Using Codeigniter and Rest Api's <u>imamiamedics</u>
- Buns Master
  - Using Codeigniter, Rest API'S http://bunsmasterrichmond.ca/
- ERP System

https://xenithservices.com/login

#### **SUMMARY**

Hello, I am Noman Ali, a seasoned developer with a wealth of experience in creating and customizing PHP applications. My expertise extends to the latest PHP frameworks, including Codelgniter and Laravel 6, 7, and 8. I specialize in developing both small and large-scale business software solutions .In addition to my proficiency in PHP, I have a strong command of Node.js, MongoDB, and modern front-end technologies such as React.js and Vue.js.

## **Work Experience**



#### **Genetech Solutions**

Software Developer Laravel | Codeigniter | CMS | Nodejs | VueJs | API'S AI 09/2022 – 07/2024



#### **Human Rights justice and defenders**

Contract Project Laravel | Php | Sql 06/2022 – 08/2022



#### **Toyota Motor Corporation**

Contract Project Laravel | Php | Sql 03/2022 - 06/2022



## Gexton

Full Stack Developer Instructor | Laravel | Php | Sql 07/2021 – 02/2022



#### Web Developer

G.D.H

Rest Api's | ThreeJs | Clara.io | Php | Codeigniter 01/2018 - 03/2019

## **Education**



## **Bachelor of Information Technology**

Institution: Sindh University Jamshoro 02/2018 - 04/2021



#### **Intermediate**

Government Degree College Qazi Amhed, Mehar 2016,



#### Matriculation

Government Higher Secondary School K.N Shah 2015,

## Languages

- English
- Urdu
- Proficiency
- Proficiency

## **Interest**

- Research
- Language

Sports

Chess

## **SIGNATURE**

noman